var questions = [{
 "question":"In what city was Jesus born?",
 "option1": "Jerusalem",
 "option2": "Bethlehem",
 "option3": "Bethsaida",
 "option4": "Golgota",
 "answer": "2"
},{
 "question":"How many books are in the New Testament?",
 "option1": "20",
 "option2": "33",
 "option3": "27",
 "option4": "40",
 "answer": "3"
},{
 "question":"What type of insect did John the Baptist eat in the desert?",
 "option1": "Butterflies",
 "option2": "Mosquitoes",
 "option3": "Beetles",
 "option4": "Locusts",
 "answer": "4"
},{
 "question":"Who were the first apostles called to follow Jesus?",
 "option1": "Peter and Andrew",
 "option2": "Peter and James",
 "option3": "Peter and Philip",
 "option4": "Peter and Judas",
 "answer": "1"
},{
 "question":"How many people did Jesus feed with five loaves of bread and two fish?",
 "option1": "about 3000 men",
 "option2": "about 4000 men",
 "option3": "about 5000 men",
 "option4": "about 6000 men",
 "answer": "3"
},{
 "question":"After Jesus was arrested, which apostle disowned him three times?",
 "option1": "James",
 "option2": "Philip",
 "option3": "Judas",
 "option4": "Peter",
 "answer": "4"
},{
 "question":"Who recognized Jesus as the Messiah when he was presented at the Temple as a baby?",
 "option1": "Simon",
 "option2": "Peter",
 "option3": "Simeon",
 "option4": "John the Baptist",
 "answer": "3"
},{
 "question":"Who asked Pilate for Jesus' body after the crucifixion?",
 "option1": "Joseph of Arimathea",
 "option2": "Mary Magdalene",
 "option3": "Peter",
 "option4": "Philip",
 "answer": "1"
},{
 "question":"Paul was shipwrecked on what island?",
 "option1": "Patmos",
 "option2": "Malta",
 "option3": "Seychelles",
 "option4": "Madagasca",
 "answer": "2"
},{
 "question":"What is the shortest book in the New Testament?",
 "option1": "Jude",
 "option2": "1 John",
 "option3": "2 John",
 "option4": "3 John",
 "answer": "3"

}]